Big victory tonight in Virginia
where the voters of the Commonwealth
have helped to stop the mega power grab.
Donald Trump and the extremist, they
started this redistricting war, but we
made clear from the very beginning that
we would finish it.
And that's exactly what we continue to
do. We won prop 50 in California, pushed
them back in Ohio, stopped them in New
Hampshire, stopped them in Indiana,
picked up a seat in Utah, stopped them
in Kansas, stopped them in Nebraska, and
tonight we won a big victory in
Virginia. These clowns have been playing
checkers and we're going to continue to
play three-dimensional chess. When they
go low, we hit back hard.